[
    {"question": "Statistical technique used to determine if a test is actually measuring what it is intended to measure.", "answer": "Validity"},
    {"question": "According to Freud, the area of the psyche where unknown wishes and needs are kept that play a significant role in our conscious behavior.", "answer": "Unconscious"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Unconditioned Stimulus"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Unconditioned Response"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Unconditional Positive Regard"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Transference"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Temperament"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Synapse"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Superego"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Self Actualization"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Schema"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Reliability"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Reinforcer"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Punishment"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Object Permanence"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Neurotransmitter"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Long Term Memory"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Locus of Control"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Introversion"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Intelligence Quotient [IQ]"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Independent Variable"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Id"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Hallucination"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Free Association"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Extroversion"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Episodic Memory"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Ego"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Double Blind Study"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Dependent Variable"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Delusion"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Confound"},
    {"question": "Who wrote Hamlet?", "answer": "Collective Unconscious"}
]
